Guide to the David Trinidad Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS.106
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Publications
  - Subseries C: Magazines 1976-1998
    - POETRY/LA. No. 2; spring/summer 1981.Poem: "Hecate." POETRY NOW. Vol. 7, No. 1; 1982. Poems: "We Dream of Snakes," "The Boy" [see Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 10], 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - L.A WEEKLY. November 13-18 1981. (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - NEW AGE. Vol. 7, No. 10; May 1982. Poem: "Pavane.", 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - SOUTH BAY MAGAZINE. January 1982 Poem: "In a Suburb of Thebes.", 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9a)
    - BARNEY. No. 4; spring 1984. Poems: "Poem" ("That vast dance floor.. ."), "Song," "Window Seat." (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - IN TOUCH. No. 97; November 1984. Poem: "Tim's Stolen Sweater.", 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - MR. MALE REVIEW. Vol. 2, No. 1; July 1985. - Poem: "Up & Down"., 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - NORTHRIDGE REVIEW. Vol. 4, No. 1; spring 1986. Answers to questionnaire., 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - STROKE. Vol. 9, No. 2; 1989. Poem: "My Lover". (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - INSTANT CLASSICS (Poetry Postcard Project). Vol. 1; fall 1989. Poem: "Violin"., 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - THE POETRY PROJECT NEWSLETTER. No. 138; 1990. Poem: "At the End of the Dream I Can Fly". (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - SANTA MONICA REVIEW. Vol. 3., No. 1; fall 1990. Poem: "The Wanderer"., 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - COLORADO NORTH REVIEW. Vol. 32, Numbers 3 & 4; 1991. Poems: "Housesitting at Joan's," "Translation". THE JAMES WHITE REVIEW. Vol. 8, No. 3; spring 1991. Poem: "Pee Shy" [see Oversize, IV N, F. 12] (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - NEW DELTA REVIEW. Vol. 8, No. 2; spring/summer 1991. Interview: "An Interview with David Trinidad" by Janet Wondra. Poems: "What Debbie and Cameron Lost in New York," "Last Night," "Yvette. Mimieux in Hit Lady". Judge of Eyster Prize (Poetry). (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - IT CAME FROM THE GROG. Vol. 1; No. 3; 1991. Poems: "It's Not Unusual," "Subway," "Alcoholic," "At An Opening" - (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - OUTWEEK. No. 97; May 8, 1991. Interview: "Playing with Dolls: Games with David Trinidad" by Joan Larkin. Poem: "Answer Song" - (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - HARPER'S. Vol. 283, No. 1695; August 1991. Poem: from "Reruns". THE JAMES WHITE REVIEW. Vol. 9, No. 1; fall 1991. Guest Poetry Editor [see Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 13]. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - BLUEBOY. Vol. 2, No. 12; December 1991. Poem: "Monday, Monday"., 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - GIRLJOCK. Summer 1992. Poem: "The 10 Best Episodes of The Patty Duke Show". (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - COLORADO NORTH REVIEW. Vol. 33, Numbers 1 & 2; 1992. Poems: "Early Days," "Ghosts". (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - THE HERMAN REVIEW. No. 1; 1992. Poem: "At An Opening" - (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - SANTA MONICA REVIEW. Vol. 5, No. 1; fall 1992. Poem: "The Shower Scene in Psycho"., 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - THE ILLINOIS REVIEW. Vol. 1, No. 1; fall 1993. Poems: "The Ten Best Episodes of The Patty Duke Show," "3 a.m.," "Family. Portrait, 1963". CUPS. August 1994. Poem: "Sunday Evening"[removed to Downtown Periodicals]. THE ILLINOIS REVIEW. Vol. 2, No. 2; spring 1995. Poem: "Cinnamon Toast". THE ILLINOIS REVIEW. Vol. 3, Numbers 1 & 2; fall 1995/spring 1996. Piece: "Bewitched"., 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - NO ROSES REVIEW. No. 6; spring 1996. Poem: "Pink Poems". (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - THE SPOON RIVER POETRY REVIEW. Vol. 22, No. 1; winter/spring 1997. Poem: "Essay with Movable Parts". (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - SONORA REVIEW. No. 35; fall/winter 1997. Poem: "Arabesque, Gambit, Caprice, Charade and Mirage" - (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - THE ANTHOLOGIST. Spring 1998. Featured Faculty. Poems: "Red Parade," "Fortunes," "Chatty Cathy Villanelle," "Monster Mash," "Of. Mere Plastic," "Pink Poems". (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - NEW AMERICAN WRITING. No. 16; 1998. Poem: "Garbo's Trolls" - (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - THE GERM. No. 2; summer 1998. Poem: "Evening Twilight". (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - PEARL. No. 27; fall/winter 1998. Poem: "Of Mere Plastic". FOURTEEN HILLS. Vol. 5, No. 1; fall/winter 1998. Poem: "The Late Show" - (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - FOURTEEN HILLS. Vol. 5, No. 1; fall/winter 1998. Poem: "The Late Show". (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Subseries D: Poems Translated
    - Italy. Spazio Umano, 1986. "Poem" ("again like never I feel"), "Tim's Stolen Sweater.", 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - France. Changer L'Amerique: Anthologie de la Poesie Protestataire des USA (1980-1995). "Driving Back from New Haven." (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Series IV: Miscellaneous
  - Subseries A: Reviews of Books, Interviews, Articles About, Mentions
    - REVIEWS. Pavane., undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - REVIEWS. Monday, Monday. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 15], undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - REVIEWS. Living Doll., undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - REVIEWS. November., undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - REVIEWS. Pavane (1988). (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - REVIEWS. Three Stories., undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - REVIEWS. A Taste of Honey., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - REVIEWS. Hand Over Heart. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 16], undated (Box 9, Folder 8a.)
    - REVIEWS. Hand Over Heart. in Parnassus: Poetry in Review; Vol. 18, No. 2, and Vol. 19, No. 1; 1993. (Box 9, Folder 8b.)
    - REVIEWS. Answer Song. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 17], undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - REVIEWS. Anthologies., undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - INTERVIEWS., undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - ARTICLES ABOUT., undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - MENTIONS., undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - MENTIONS. (cont'd), undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Articles/Books DT Mentioned In
    - Stephen Adams. Poetic Designs: An Introduction to Meters, Verse Forms and Figures of Speech. Broadview Press, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Kim Addonizio and Dorianne Laux. The Poet's Companion: A Guide to the Pleasures of Writing Poetry. Norton, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Kathleen Aguero and Marie Harris. A Gift of Tongues: Critical Challenges in American Poetry ("In Search of a Muse: The Politics of Gay Poetry"). University of Georgia Press, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Graham Caveney and Elizabeth Young. Shopping in Space: Essays on American "Blank Generation" Fiction. Serpent's Tail, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Douglas Crase. "A Voice Like the Day" (on James Schuyler). Poetry; January 1994. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bruce Hainley. "Bruce Hainley on Joe Brainard." Frieze; May 1996., 1996, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - David E. James. "Poetry/Punk/Production: Some Recent Writing in L.A." --The Minnesota Review; fall 1984., 1984-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - David Kaufmann. "Subjectivity and Disappointment in Contemporary American Poetry." Ploughshares; Vol. 17, No. 4; winter 1991-92., 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - --"The Questions of Postmodernism." AWP Chronicle; December 1994. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - --"The Questions of Postmodernism." Jacket #4; on internet, May 1998., 1998-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Carl Little. "An Interview with James Schuyler." Agni 37; 1993. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Robert McDowell. "The Poetry Anthology." The Hudson Review; winter 1990. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Robert Peters. The Great American Poetry Bake-Off. Scarecrow Press, 1982. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Robert Peters. The Peters Black and Blue Guide to Current Literary Journals ("Little Caesar"). Cherry Valley Editions, 1983., 1983-1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Susan Wheeler. Comments in oblek 12: Writing from the New Coast: Technique; spring/fall 1993. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subseries C: Poems by others. [materials are in one folder]
    - Poems Dedicated to DT; Dennis Cooper. Ghost Stories.; Meg Daly. "Monday."; Meg Daly. "Sheer Poetry."; Connie Deanovich. "The Quest for Barbie."; Elaine Equi. "Pink Shutters."; Elaine Equi. "That Touch of Kitsch."; Amy Gerstler. "Innocence."; Amy Gerstler. "Water and Flowers."; Janet Gray. "He's So Fine."; Gerrit Henry. "Some of These Days."; Patricia Spears Jones. "Back when Roberta was the same age as Lucille."; Kevin Killian. "For David Trinidad."; James Krusoe. "Inventory."; Joan Larkin. "Brooklyn Morning."; Michael Lassell. "How to Write a Poem."; Peter Money. "Confessional."; Meredith Schuman. "Doll Stories."; James Schuyler. "Mood Indigo."; Robyn Selman. "Essay in the Form of a Russian Doll."; Susan Wheeler. "Smokes."; Rachel Zuker. "Schuyler Got 65 Grand for His Archives.", undated (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_aabb6908085a5f79c340d43367b81cb1)
  - Subseries D: Works by others [materials are in one folder]
    - Works DT Appears In; Dodie Bellamy. Tab with Jimmy. Tom Carey. "Collateral Damage." Tom Carey. "Itinerary." Lynn Crosbie. Paul's Case. Insomniac Press, 1997.; Meg Daly. "Sestina." Tim Dlugos. G-9. Tim Dlugos. "Ordinary Time." Tim Dlugos. "Trinidad." Elaine Equi. "Art About Fear." Bob Flanagan. Fuck Journal. Hanuman Books, 1987.; Allen Ginsberg. "After Class." Eloise Klein Healy. "Underground at The Hollywood Police Garage." James Schuyler. The Diary of James Schuyler. Black Sparrow Press, 1997. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_bb40de8d7b6d73f9a66f5120464bb823)
  - Subseries E: Readings 1978-1998
    - 1978-1988. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1978-1988. (cont'd) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1988-1989. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 1993 [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 18] (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Subseries F: Teaching 1987-1998
    - BEYOND BAROQUE WORKSHOP 1987. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - BEYOND BAROQUE WORKSHOP 1988. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ST. MARK'S WORKSHOP 1991. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - BROOKLYN COLLEGE 1988-1992. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - THE WRITER'S VOICE 1989-1996. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - NEW SCHOOL 1994-1996. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - HUDSON VALLEY WORKSHOP FALL 1996. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY 1996-1998. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY FALL 1996. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY SPRING 1997. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY FALL 1997. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY SPRING 1998. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY FALL 1998. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - WRITERS AT RUTGERS 1996-1998. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - WRITERS AT RUTGERS 1996-1998. (cont'd) (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - WRITERS AT RUTGERS DINNERS., undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - WRITERS AT RUTGERS PRESS RELEASES., undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - WRITERS AT RUTGERS INVOICES., undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - WRITERS AT RUTGERS BUDGET. WRITERS AT RUTGERS POSTERS. [removed to Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 19], undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - NEW SCHOOL MFA 1996-1998. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - NEW SCHOOL MFA FALL 1997. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - NEW SCHOOL MFA FALL 1998. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - BARD COLLEGE SUMMER 1998. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - GRADE BOOK (Rutgers and New School) 1996-1998. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - STUDENT RECOMMENDATIONS., undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - STUDENT RECOMMENDATIONS., undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - JOBS APPLIED TO 1994-1998. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous
    - SHERWOOD PRESS. SHERWOOD PRESS BOOKS. Rachel Sherwood., undated (Box 11, Folder 1a.)
    - Dennis Cooper. My Mark., undated (Box 11, Folder 1b.)
    - Bob Flanagan. The Wedding of Everything., undated (Box 11, Folder 1c.)
    - CONTESTS JUDGED., undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - POEMS SUBMITTED LOG., undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - GRANTS. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 20], undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - RESUME., undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - DT BIOGRAPHY., undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - BILLY SULLIVAN DRAWING OF DT 1998. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - BROOKLYN COLLEGE MFA., undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - BROOKLYN COLLEGE NOTEBOOK 1988. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - COLLEGE DIPLOMAS. (California State), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - COLLEGE DIPLOMAS. (Brooklyn College), undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - DT ASTROSCOPE., undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - DT/IRA SILVERBERG GUEST BOOK 1992-1998. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - AA/SPIRITUAL., undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - FROM AA INVENTORIES., undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - GRATITUDE LISTS., undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - MISCELLANEOUS. Includes driver's licenses, college transcripts, diplomas, etc., undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Subseries H: Notebooks 1984-1998
    - February 1984-June 1984., 1984-1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - November 1985. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Circa June 1986-December 1986., 1986-1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - December 1986-September 1987., 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Circa November 1987-Circa May 1988., 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - November 1987-October 1988., 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - November 1988-July 1989., 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - August 1989-September 1990., 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - August 1990-October 1991., 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - October 1991-August 1992., 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - August 1992-January 1994., 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - March 1994-May 1995., 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - May 1995-May 1997., 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - May 1997-October 1997., 1997-1997 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - October 1997-August 1998., 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Subseries I: Date Books 1987-1998
    - 1987 [removed to Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 21] (Box 12, Folder **)
    - 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Subseries J: Photographs [see also Oversize]
    - BOX OF SLIDES (taken by Gail Kasynski, mid-80s), [1985] (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - PHOTOGRAPHS: "The Other Jackie" (Jacqueline Susann Panel, Oct. 1997) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Subseries K: Videorecordings
    Conditions Governing Access
    Video recordings have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - Poetry Center, SF, 3/1/90, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Thin Air, Volume 16, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Hanuman Presents, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - A&E Artist of the Week, 4/27/97, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Subseries M: Childhood Material
    - CHILDHOOD (SCHOOL), undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - CHILDHOOD (ART), undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - CHILDHOOD (CHURCH), undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - CHILDHOOD (BIRTH), undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - CHILDHOOD (CARDS), undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - CHILDHOOD (VALENTINES), undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - CHILDHOOD (MISC.) [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 24], undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Subseries N: Oversize Items
    - Book Review: Ceremonies, Essex Hemphill. Voice Literary Supplement; June 1992. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Book Review: Tasker Street, Mark Halliday. Voice Literary Supplement; November 1992. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Book Review: Miss Pamela's Mercy, Lynn Crosbie. Voice Literary Supplement; March 1993. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Book Reviews: "Line Breaks" (Bent Antenna, Curt Anderson; The Red Line, Betsy Sholl; Vox Angelica, Timothy Liu; Smile!, Denise Duhamel). Los Angeles Reader; April 1993. "Line Breaks" (Wife, Jim Cory; Ted, Ron Padgett; My Tokyo, Frederick Seidel). Los Angeles Reader; July 1993. "Line Breaks" (The Descent of Alette, Alice Notley). Los Angeles Reader; October 1993. "Line Breaks" (Joan Jobe Smith, Jehovah Jukebox). Los Angeles Reader; December 1993. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Book Review: Forever Barbie: The Unauthorized Biography of a Real Doll, M.G. Lord. New York Newsday; November 20, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Book Review: Our Paris: Sketches from Memory, Edmund White. New York Newsday; November 19, 1995. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Interview: "Dream of Life: Patti Smith Gets Carried Away." Los Angeles Reader; April 29, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Essay: "In the Midnight Hour: Helter Skelter Turns Twenty-Five." Los Angeles Reader; October 1994. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Writings: "Influences: Anne Sexton." Voice Literary Supplement; April 1994. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - POETRY NOW. Vol. 7, No. 1; 1982. Poems: "We Dream of Snakes," "The Boy" (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - AVENU. Vol. 18, No. 3; winter 1989. Poems: "Warm Winter," We Dream of Snakes," "Pavane" (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - THE JAMES WHITE REVIEW. Vol. 8, No. 3; spring 1991. Poem: "Pee Shy" (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - THE JAMES WHITE REVIEW. Vol. 9, No. 1; fall 1991. Guest Poetry Editor (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - CHIRON REVIEW. Vol. 11, No. 4; winter 1992. Poem: "Wednesday Morning" (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - REVIEWS. Monday, Monday., undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - REVIEWS. Hand Over Heart., undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - REVIEWS. Answer Song., undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Readings: 1993 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - WRITERS AT RUTGERS POSTERS, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - GRANTS, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Date Book: 1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - 2 photos of DT by Ron Faranovich (Los Angeles, 1982) (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Photo of DT, IS & Damon Krukowski by Naomi Yang (Las Vegas, 1998) (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Neighborhood Rhythms (LP), undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Stork News, July 1953 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Childhood Drawing (1962) (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Jim Isermann cover for November (not used), undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Tim's Stolen Sweater (broadsides), undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Accretions 2002. Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence 1970-2002
    - Ames, Lois, undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 1)
    - Anagnopoulis, Kostas., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 2)
    - Beaumont, Jeanne., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 3)
    - Berman, Tosh., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 4)
    - Bernstein, Charles., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 5)
    - Berrigan, Anselm., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 6)
    - Black, Sophie Cabot., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 7)
    - Burrier-Backer, Rebecca., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 8)
    - Carr, Robin., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 9)
    - Clawson, Robert., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 10)
    - Coleman, Wanda., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 11)
    - Coleman, Wanda. "Love-ins with Nietzsche" (signed copy), undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 12)
    - Conley, Dianne., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 13)
    - Conrad, C.A., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 14)
    - Conrad, C.A. "Evaporate Again"., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 15)
    - Conway, Jeffrey., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 16)
    - Conway, Jeffrey., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 17)
    - Cooper, Bernard., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 18)
    - Cooper, Dennis., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 19)
    - Corbett, William., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 20)
    - Corbett, William. "Back and Forth" (inscribed copy), undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 21)
    - Corbett, William. "S2"., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 22)
    - Cory, Jim., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 23)
    - Creeley, Robert., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 24)
    - Crosbie, Lynn., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 25)
    - Crosbie, Lynn., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 26)
    - Crosbie, Lynn., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 27)
    - Crosbie, Lynn., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 28)
    - Crosbie, Lynn. The Honeymoon Killers/Look Homeward Angel" (inscribed)., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 29)
    - Crosbie, Lynn. "I Eat Your Flesh" (inscribed)., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 30)
    - Crowley, Mart., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 31)
    - Crowley, Mart. "Eloise Takes a Bath" by Kay Thompson., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 32)
    - Daly, Meg., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 33)
    - Deanorich, Connie., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 34)
    - Devereaux, Jean., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 35)
    - Dlugos, Tim., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 36)
    - Doris, Stacey., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 37)
    - Drizhal, Peter., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 38)
    - Duhamel, Denise., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 39)
    - Edgar, Chris., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 40)
    - Elledge, Jim., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 41)
    - Epperson, John., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 42)
    - Equi, Elaine., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 43)
    - Equi, Elaine. Prose manuscripts (typed copies of)., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 44)
    - Equi, Elaine. Poems., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 45)
    - Faranovich, Ron., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 46)
    - Fergusen, Scott., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 47)
    - Field, Edward., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 48)
    - Ford, Michael C., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 49)
    - Foye, Raymond., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 50)
    - Friedman, Ed., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 51)
    - Frideman, Michael., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 52)
    - Galassi, Jonathan., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 53)
    - Gerstler, Amy., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 54)
    - Gerstler, Amy., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 55)
    - Gizzi, Peter., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 56)
    - Gluck, Robert., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 57)
    - Hall, Donald., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 58)
    - Hannah, Duncan., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 59)
    - Harlan-Fero, Liz., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 60)
    - Harris, Jana., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 61)
    - Healy, Eloise Klein., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 62)
    - Hell, Richard., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 63)
    - Hoover, Paul., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 64)
    - Houston-Montgomery, Beauregard., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 65)
    - Howland, Rebecca., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 66)
    - Indigo., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 67)
    - Jansen, Sharon., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 68)
    - Jones, Patricia Spears., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 69)
    - Katz, Joy., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 70)
    - Katz, Vincent., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 71)
    - Kaufman, Alan., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 72)
    - Kelleher, Mike., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 73)
    - Kernan, Nathan., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 74)
    - Killian, Kevin., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 75)
    - Killian, Kevin.. "Mirage #4/Period[ical]" no. 84 w/ letter to DT., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 76)
    - Killian, Kevin.. "Mirage #4/Period[ical]" no. 85 w/ letter to DT., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 77)
    - Killian, Kevin.. "Mirage #4/Period[ical]" no. 86 w/ letter to DT., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 78)
    - Killian, Kevin.. "Mirage #4/Period[ical]" no. 90 w/ letter to DT., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 79)
    - Kobosa, David., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 80)
    - Koestenbaum, Wayne., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 81)
    - Kohn Michels, Victoria., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 82)
    - Kralick, John E., undated (Box 2002.01, Folder 83)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1973 (Box 2002.01, Folder 84)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1974 (Box 2002.01, Folder 85)
    - Kralick, John E., 1975 (Box 2002.01, Folder 86)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1976 (Box 2002.01, Folder 87)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1977 (Box 2002.01, Folder 88)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1978 (Box 2002.02, Folder 89)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1979 (Box 2002.02, Folder 90)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1980 (Box 2002.02, Folder 91)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1981 (Box 2002.02, Folder 92)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1982 (Box 2002.02, Folder 93)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1983 (Box 2002.02, Folder 94)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1986 (Box 2002.02, Folder 95)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1987 (Box 2002.02, Folder 96)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1988 (Box 2002.02, Folder 97)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1989 (Box 2002.02, Folder 98)
    - Kralick, John E. DT to 1990s, ca. 1990 (Box 2002.02, Folder 99)
    - Kralick, John E., undated (Box 2002.02, Folder 100)